我已經跟你說過了
我剛收到哥哥的來信
他在美國挺好的
他問候你  爹
你已經沒有哥哥了
拳匪
Boxers!
不準再往前一步
Not one step further.
玉璽的保管人
The keeper of the Imperial Seal.
我正在找你
just the man I was looking for.
女人
A woman.
你們中國人真前衛
You Chinese are very progressive.
這是老朋友送你的禮物
A gift from an old friend.
烏義
Wu Chow.
他要我代他問候你一聲
He wanted me to send his regards.
爹
Father!
Father.
爹
玉璽  你必須拿回來
The seal. You must get it back.
我保證
I promise.
把這個...
Give this...
交給你的哥哥
to your brother.
你在看什麼?
What are you reading?
洛依大戰木乃伊
Oh. "Roy O'Bannon vs. The Mummy".
真令人難以置信
It's incredible. Roy's just taken out
洛依只用一顆子彈
the Mummy's entire army confederate soldiers,
就解決了殭屍大軍
and he only had one bullet.
不可能
That's impossible.
可能的
Oh, no, It's not.
洛依找出峽谷的彈射點
Roy figured out the physics of the canyon
用一發子彈
and then ricocheted a bullet off the canyon wall.
就射穿所有殭屍的心臟
Nailed each zombie through the heart.
那個上海佬呢?
What about the Shanghai Kid?
他在幫洛依擦手槍時
He was captured and knocked out on page 10
被打昏綁走了
while he was polishing Roy's pearl handles.
別擔心
Don't you worry.
在他快被獻祭之前
Roy's about to save him
洛依救了他
from becoming a human sacrifice.
這故事都是胡扯
Those stories are all lies.
不  背後有寫
No. See? It says right here on the back.
作者塞奇·麥卡利斯特寫作本書的根據
Author Sage McCallister bases all his stories
均為第一手資料
on firsthand accounts.
抱歉  警長  沒公主
Sorry, sheriff. No princess.
你每天都遇到正午的驛站馬車
Every day you meet the noon stage.
結果都一樣
Every day It's the same story.
她不會回來了
She's not coming back.
佩佩在舊金山全心工作
Pei Pei's married to her work in San Francisco.
現代女性
Modern woman.
警長  你有包裹
Sheriff, you got a parcel.
也許是她寄來的
Hey, maybe It's from her!
不  是我在中國的妹妹寄的
No. It's from my sister in China.
我理解
I know.
我知道  但一定要去
I know. I must go.
待在這兒
Stay here and be a
好好服侍新警長
good horsey for the new sheriff.
警長  那輛馬車往東去了
Uh, sheriff, that stage is headed east.
中國不是在西邊嗎?
Isn't China kind of west of here?
我要去紐約  不是中國
I'm not going to China. I'm going to New York.
洛依拿了我的錢去投資
Roy invested my money.
他是不是真的
Is it true that he lives in a penthouse
住在麗池飯店閣樓
at the top of the Ritz surrounded by
還有很多美女伺候他?
dozens of beautiful women at his every beck and call?
那是以前的他
That's the old Roy.
他現在結婚成家了
He's married, settled down.
相信我  他已經變了
Trust me, he's changed.
我們那時候以寡敵眾
So there we were. Completely outnumbered.
毫無生機
He didn't have to tell me we didn't stand a chance.
我讓上海佬跟公主先走
So I send the Shanghai Kid and the princess out the back.
可憐的上海佬嚇壞了
Poor Shanghai Kid. He was so frightened.
完全忘了謝我救他一命
He forgot to thank me for saving his life.
反正我習慣了
I'm used to that.
返回前線數到三...
Now, I returned to the front, and I counted to three...
我就開火了
and I burst out of the mission.
扣下扳機  子彈四處亂飛
Pearl handles blazing. Lead flying everywhere.
但沒有一顆能傷到我
And not a single bullet touched me.
-真的嗎?  -真的
- No! - Yeah.
那皇帝的金子呢?
What happened to the emperor's gold?
平分了
Well, we divided it up.
我堅持把自己那份給了印地安人
I insisted on giving my share to the Indians.
給了野蠻人?
The savages?
不要稱那些高貴的人野蠻
Please Don't ever call those noble people savages.
要是自豪於自己的身體
If being proud of your body and wanting to
認為赤身裸體騎馬的就是野蠻人
ride around naked all day makes you a savage,
那你正在跟野蠻人喝酒
then, by God, you're drinking with a savage.
這是所謂的3P
And that is what you call a French toast.
你真見多識廣
You are so sophisticated, Mr. O'Bannon.
誰還想來點香檳?
Who's up for some more bubbly?
舉手  洛依
Reach for the sky, Roy.
什麼?
Say that again.
把手舉起來  洛依
Reach for the sky, Roy.
姜文  你這個狡猾的傢伙
Chon Wen! You sly son of a gun!
-瞧瞧你!  -也瞧瞧你!
- Look at you! - Look at you!
什麼風把你吹來紐約的?
What brings you to New York?
我那一份黃金
My share of the gold.
說清楚  什麼黃金?
Refresh my memory. What gold?
皇帝的黃金
The emperor's gold.
那筆黃金目前正在做
Okay, now, that gold is in what the
所謂的長期投資
Wall Street pros call a long-term investment.
正在升值  不能取出來
We can't touch it because It's building.
我今晚就要
I need it tonight.
來都來了  慶祝一下吧
You just got here. Let's celebrate.
沒時間
No. I don't have time.
你才剛到啊
You just got to the big city.
我父親被殺害了
My father's been killed.
姜
Chon, I'm...
你需要錢回去奔喪
You need the money to get back for the funeral?
我要去英國
No. I must go to England.
船今晚就開
The ship leaves tonight.
-你父親死在英國?  -中國
- Your father died in England? -China
我妹妹追蹤兇手到了倫敦
My sister followed the murderer to London.
兇手?
Wait. Murderer.
我全搞混了
I'm a little bit mixed up.
讓我搞清楚
Let me see if I can get the facts straight.
你有妹妹?
You have a sister?
你沒跟我說過你有個妹妹
You never told me you had a sister.
長的好看嗎  還是像你?
Is she pretty or does she look like you?
說實話
Be honest.
洛依  我需要我的錢
Roy, I need my money!
我不喜歡你的態度
I don't like that tone of voice.
我們共患難過
You think after all we've been through
難道我會坑你?
I'd stiff you?
我現在混得可好了
I'm doing pretty well for myself.
-對不起  -沒關係
- I'm sorry, Roy. - That's okay.
你正面對難關
You're going through a really tough time right now.
得更信任別人
You got to be more trusting of people, okay?
我是誰?  洛依!
Look at me. It's Roy.
五號桌的夫婦要點菜
The couple at table 5 is ready to order.
你在這兒工作?
Do you work here?
才不是呢
No, I don't work here.
這些人老愛跟我穿一樣
It looks like these guys are wearing a similar Jacket.
這是你的小費
Roy, here's your cut of the tips.
真是莫名奇妙!
It's the craziest thing.
我這麼常來  還老把我當侍應生
I guess because I come in here so much
真是討厭
they're mistaking me for a waiter. It's embarrassing.
你把黃金花光了
You lost the gold.
-不是全部  -剩下的呢?
- Not all of it. - Where's the rest?
一句話  齊柏林飛船
I have one word for you. Zeppelin.
我現在就要我的錢
I need my money now!
別激動
Easy, easy.
你願意為這筆錢赴湯蹈火?
Will you do anything for this money?
願意  我今晚就得起程
Yes. I must leave tonight.
好  拿着這把鑰匙
Okay. Take this key.
去間房裡好好梳洗一下
Go to the room. Get cleaned up.
老朋友我自有妙計  快去
Your old pal Roy's got a plan. Go! Come on!
你好啊  猛男
Howdy, big boy.
裏面有個女人
What? There's a woman in there!
要我陪她睡覺
She wants me to sleep with her.
當然羅  我跟她說...
Of course she does, I told her...
中國偉大的地方
the Great Wall ain't the only big thing
不僅僅是長城
coming out of China.
你幹嘛這麼說?
Why did you say that?
好讓你賺錢
So you could get the money.
我不會為錢陪女人睡覺
I will not sleep with women for money!
為什麼不?  我就陪
Why? I'm gonna sleep with her for money.
姜  儘管去做
Chon, just go in there and do your business
想想你在英國的妹妹吧
and think about your sister in England.
-什麼?  -洛依
- What? - Roy!
-該上工了  -洛依
- Duty calls. - Roy!
晚上好  市長先生
Good evening, Mr.Mayor.
-她們人呢?  -誰?
- Where are they? - Who?
我的女兒們
My daughters.
10樓
10th floor.
洛依  你有麻煩了
Roy? Roy, you got trouble.
洛依!
Roy!
我還有點事
I got to check on something.
去去就回
I'll be right back.
姜  我們得趕快離開
Chon, new plan. We got to go.
你在幹什麼?
Chon, what are you doing?!
我在幫她整脊
I'm fixing her back.
把她放下  你這個變態
Put her down, you decadent Philistine.
姜  快  我們走
Hey, Chon, come on! Let's go!
快點
Come on!
我真的不懂  怎麼了?
I don't understand. What's going on?
沒時間解釋
I don't have time to explain.
你只要知道
All you have to know is
壞蛋在追我們
there are bad men after us...
我是好人
but I'm in the right.
-洛依  -姜  這回你得相信我
- Roy. -Chon, You gotta trust me on this.
好吧  聽着
Okay, look.
我的人生正在轉變
I'm in a transitional phase in my life.
-但是 -但是什麼?
- But, - But what?
你想聽實話?
You want to know the truth?
我現在有點迷失
I'm a little lost right now. I see you.
你比較有目標  但你看看我
You've got a sense of purpose. But look at me.
我是個30歲的服務生兼牛郎
I'm a 30-year-old waiter gigolo.
我有什麼未來?
Where's the future in that?
你有什麼計劃?
So what's the plan?
你一直都是我的指南針
You were always my compass, Chon.
你問對問題了
The plan. You ask me the right questions.
我的計劃是
The plan? The plan, I think,
娶個妻子
is to find the right woman.
生很多孩子  教養他們
Raise a lot of children and teach them values.
不  洛依  是脫身計劃
No, Roy. The plan to get out of here.
好吧  脫身計劃
Okay, the plan. Here we go.
-警察  警察  -他們能幫我們
- Cops! Cops! - They can help us.
這些警察不行
No, no. Chon, not these cops.
他們手腳不幹凈
These are dirty cops.
愛佔便宜
They take advantage of people.
要是他們攔下我們  記住...
Now, if they stop us, remember...
我不是洛依
I'm not Roy O'Bannon.
那是誰?
Who are you?
是你朋友
I'm your friend
西部來的亡命之徒
Smoky Desperado from the West.
那我又是誰?
And who am I?
你是鬍鬚張
You. You're Benihana.
-鬍鬚張  -是的
- Benihana. - Yeah.
你在城裡教殘障孩童瑜伽
You teach crippled children yoga here in the city.
你先走
You go first.
不  為什麼是我?
No! Why me?
因為你比較不起眼
Because you blend in, okay?
快去  別讓他們看見你
Now, go! Don't let them see you.
鬍鬚張
Benihana.
姜!
Psst! Chon!
快  別浪費時間了
Come on. Stop wasting time.
你!
You!
我找到離開的辦法了
Chon, I found our ticket out of here.
上路了
We're on our way.
洛依又逢凶化吉
Looks like old Roy came through again.
跟以前一樣
just like old times, Chon.
你檢查那邊
Man, Check over there!
-那邊  -胡同方向!
- Over to the alley. - That way!
是啊  跟以前一樣
Yeah, just like old times.
忘了黃金吧
Will you forget about the gold for a second?
等齊柏林飛船起飛
You're gonna have more money than you ever
你就發了
dreamed of when that first zeppelin takes off.
為什麼我總得相信你?
Why do I always believe you?
什麼意思?
What do you mean?
你得慶幸我沒去投資
You're lucky I didn't invest
荒唐的汽車生意
in that ridiculous automobile idea.
那會賺很多錢
Yeah, That's gonna make a lot of money.
幹什麼?
What's that?
失寵了  我失寵了
Doghouse. I'm in the doghouse.
拜託  姜
Oh, come on, Chon.
抱歉我說謊
Look, I'm sorry I lied.
我不想讓你失望
I just didn't want to disappoint you.
就是這樣
That's exactly what I mean.
你的臉真臭
I can't take that look.
我跟我父親學的
I learned it from my father.
他常這樣看我
That's how he used to look at me.
你爸是做什麼的?
What did your dad do?
禁軍侍衛?
Was he an Imperial Guard?
不  更重要的
No. Much more important.
他負責保管玉璽
He was the keeper of the Imperial Seal.
這就是我為什麼喜歡中國的原因
That's what I love about China.
每個人的工作都好有趣
Everybody's Job description sounds so damn cool.
那玉璽從成吉思汗起
The seal has been symbol of the emperor's power
就象徵皇帝的權位
since Genghis Khan.
皇帝們世代相傳
It has been passed down from one emperor to another.
我們家族已守護它十二代了
My family have been watching over it
十二代?
for 12 generations. - 12 generations?
我父親跟我常在散步時
My father and I used to skip stones across the moat
談到有天我將承襲他的工作
and talk about a day I would follow his footsteps.
我是他唯一的兒子
I was his only son.
要是我在家  就能保護他
If I'd have been there, I could have protected him.
這不是你的錯  你離家太遠了
It's not your fault. You were 3,000 miles away.
那個小盒子是什麼?
What's with that little box?
我妹寄來的  我父親留給我的
My sister sent it to me from my father.
裏面有訊息
There's a message inside.
什麼訊息?
What's it say?
這是個七巧盒
It's a puzzle box.
我打不開
I don't know how to open yet.
拿鐵鎚敲開它
What do you mean? Get a hammer and
不就能看了?
smash it open so you can see what it says.
我一定要有耐性
I must have patience.
等我能打開時
By the time I'm able to open it,
就能讀到信息了
I will be ready to read the message.
拜託  孔夫子
Come on, Confucius.
這真令人感動得熱淚盈眶
That's the corniest thing l've ever heard.
讓我看看
Let me see this.
你知道嗎?
You know what?
我們要去英國
We're gonna go to England.
找出你的殺父兇手
We're gonna find your dad's killer,
奪回玉璽
get that seal back.
這回可沒賞金
There's no reward for this, Roy.
誰說要賞金的?
Who said anything about a reward?
我說的是友誼  忠誠  榮譽
I'm talking about friendship, loyalty, honor.
對吧?
Okay?
謝謝你  洛依
Thank you, Roy.
聽說英國美眉很辣
And I hear England is ass soup.
美女很多
A lot of pretty girls there.
第一件事  各位...
First order of business, my Lords...
是我們的摯友
is a report from our esteemed friend
羅朋閣下的報告
Lord Rathbone.
他出使中國
who recently returned from
才剛回來
a diplomatic mission to China.
各位同僚...
Fellow Lords... I'm afraid
我從東方帶來令人不安的消息
I bring disturbing news from the Orient.
鴉片戰爭重創中國
The opium wars have ravaged the land.
皇帝的敵人正在醞釀起事
The emperor's enemies are organizing.
其中最糟糕的是義和團
The most vicious are the Boxers.
冷血殺人的
A godless band of rebels
無神論者
who murder without discretion.
中國的情況並不好
China is not well.
我帶了位使節回來
I have brought back an envoy
他能讓我們明白
who should give us some insight
中國人神秘的心思
into the inscrutable mind of the Chinese.
他瘋了嗎?
Is he mad?
中國皇帝送給
Given to Her MaJesty Queen Victoria
維多利亞女皇
by the emperor in recognition of her 50
祝賀她光榮即位五十周年
glorious years on the throne.
令人厭惡
Outrageousness!
女皇萬歲!
Long live the queen.
開膛手再度犯案  號外
Extra! Extra! Read all about it.
你好  朋友
Howdy, partner.
英國人不太友善
The English are not very friendly.
他們就是輸不起
They're just sore losers.
輸了什麼?
What did they lose?
小戰役  美國獨立戰爭
A little thing called the American Revolution, Chon.
沒聽說過
Never heard of it.
簡單來說
I'll give you the highlights.
他們派了百萬士兵
They came over with about a million men.
而我們卻以農夫的耙子
We had a bunch of farmers with pitchforks
把他們打得落花流水
and beat them like a drum.
嘿  這裡有行人啊!
Hey! I'm walking here!
你的車駛錯邊了!
You're driving on the wrong side of the road!
一堆菜鳥
Bunch of amateurs.
真受不了
These people don't get it.
你好  小姐們
Hello, ladies.
你看看你
Look at you.
我不該看漂亮女士嗎?
What? I'm not supposed to notice a pretty lady?
你還說
I thought you wanted to
想成家養小孩?
settle down and have a family.
我是想  希望可以嘛
I do, Chon. I just hope I can.
為什麼不行?
Why not?
我擔心以前老騎在馬背上
Sometimes I worry that all the damn horseback riding
顛簸得太厲害
I did out in the West, bouncing up and down on the hard
可能害我的蝌蚪
saddles might have made it, so my salmon
全都掛點了
Don't swim upstream the way they're supposed to.
什麼?
What?
搞不好我打的都是空包彈
I might be shooting blanks.
什麼都別說了
Don't say anything.
洛依  沒關係
Roy, It's okay.
有些人並不需要家庭
Some people are not meant to have a family.
但我好喜歡小孩
L've always had such a special connection
小淘氣
with children. The little ankle biters.
小心點  死孩子
Hey, watch it, you little punk!
抱歉  先生
Pardon me, guv.
你們是不是迷路了?
You gents lost your way?
是的  我們在找我妹妹
Yeah. We're looking for my sister.
她住牛津街32號
She's staying at 32 Oxford Street.
那裡我熟
I know it well, guv.
我父親以前住那兒
Me old man used to live there.
你能帶我們去嗎?
Can you show us the way?
我的記性不太好
Well, memory's a little dodgy.
來個五先令  應該就能搞定
But I'm sure for a bob I could get you there.
你把我們當什麼了?
What do you take us for?
我們可不是阿獃與阿瓜
Okies from Muskogee?
去唬別人吧
Go sell your bullshit someplace else.
我們不上當
We're not buying.
那就謝謝你的小費羅
Thanks for the tip, guv.
那是我從我叔叔那裡偷來的表
Hey! I stole that watch from my uncle!
什麼?
What?
往這邊
This way.
過來  你這個小臟鬼
Come here, you little rubbish eater!
我不是叫你
What did I tell you about
別碰我們的地盤嗎  查理?
poaching on our turf, Charlie?
我一直都很守規矩  真的
I'm on the straight and narrow. Honest.
那這是什麼?
What's this, then?
等我扁完你
After I'm through beating you...
你會希望
you're gonna wish
自己沒出來混
you never ran away from the workhouse!
放過那個孩子
Leave the boy alone.
死觀光客  別管閑事
Bloody tourists! Get your noses out of it!
隨你怎麼扁他
Do whatever you want to the kid,
但那懷錶是我的
but that's my watch and holder.
我們有一票人
Well, there is a load of us
你們卻只有兩個
and only two of you.
滾吧
So piss off!
別激動
Easy, fellas.
你們就是這樣才會輸給我們
You've lost one war this way.
別再犯同樣的錯誤
Don't make the same mistake twice.
追上他
Come on! After him!
他在這裡
There he is! Get him!
去逮他  快啊!
We've got him now. Move in, lads.
等等  等等
Boys, boys, wait, wait!
快啊  去逮他!
Come on! Get him!
上梯子去  快點!
Up the bloody ladder!
Oh! Watch it!
當心點!
逮住他!
Get him!
宰了他!
Come here, you!
酷
Cool.
抓住他  快點!
Move it!
你
You!
-我怎麼樣?  -還行
- Did you see that? - It's okay.
還行?  那可是我的獨家絕招!
Okay? I call that one my Kung Po Chicken.
我解決了那個混混
I clotheslined the sucker.
快讓開!
Come on, get back! Clear away!
讓開路!
Make way!
我想你們該
I think you gentlemen should
跟我回警局去
accompany me back to the yard.
這不是警局  是監獄!
This isn't a yard! It's a jail!
洛依  冷靜點
Roy, calm down.
不可思議
Unbelievable.
有人來了
Wait! Someone's coming!
讓我來處理
Let me handle this.
我來處理
I'm gonna handle it.
英國人跟你不一樣
The English aren't like you.
他們都很纖細敏感的
They don't get all emotional. Touchy-feely.
幫我個忙  別亂動手
Do me a favor. Park the kung fu.
讓我來談判
Let me do the talking.
過來  讓我抱抱你們
Come here. Let me give you a hug.
我追那群街頭幫派兩年了
L've been after that Fleet Street gang for two years.
你們兩個卻一個下午就搞定
Then you two come along and bring them down
太厲害了!
in a single afternoon. Brilliant!
我的表!
Oh, That's my watch!
一個街頭流浪兒送來的
Yes. A street urchin turned it in.
那個死小鬼  最好沒刮傷
The little punk better not have scuffed it.
我真希望你能轉運
I hope your luck picks up.
什麼意思?
What do you mean?
我從表上看出
I deduced from your watch
你走了一陣壞運
that you'd hit a rough patch.
沒錯  你怎麼知道?
He has. How do you know?
這是我發明的一種調查技巧
It's an investigative technique I've developed.
我能從一個人的私人物品
I can deduce intimate details about an individual
看出這個人的情況
through a close scrutiny of their personal effects.
你還能看出什麼?
What else can you tell?
這表的主人是個爛賭徒
The owner of this watch is a bad gambler
槍法也糟
and a lousy shot.
他雖死裡逃生過許多次
Although he's cheated death several times,
卻仍漫無目的
he spends most of his life wandering in a rather pathetic
徒勞無功地尋找目標與尊重
and futile search for purpose and respect.
有了
Oh, yes.
他喜歡隨便的女人
He has a penchant for loose women.
真是厲害
Wow. That's amazing.
我相信這在生日派對上
I'm sure It's a very popular party trick
唬小孩很有用
at birthdays for small children.
但這對大人沒用
but it doesn't quite play with adults.
搞清楚
just to set the record straight.
歐·洛依不是喜歡隨便的女人
Roy O'Bannon is not attracted to loose women.
是隨便的女人都喜歡我
Loose women are attracted to me.
-你就是歐·洛依?  -是
- You're Roy O'Bannon? - Yeah.
那個著名的西部英雄?
The famous Western folk hero?
你聽說過我?
Have you heard of me?
有沒有聽說過你?
Have I heard of you?
洛依大戰木乃伊
L've only read "Roy O'Bannon vs. The Mummy"
我看過五遍  好看極了
five times. It's fascinating.
見過上海佬
I want you to meet the Shanghai Kid.
是了  忠誠的中國助手
Oh, yes. The faithful Chinese sidekick.
我不是助手
I'm not a sidekick.
那些故事都是假的
Those stories are all lies.
別鬧脾氣了
Come on, Don't be bitter.
我又管不了塞奇·麥卡利斯特怎麼寫
I can't help what Sage McCallister writes.
有需要我效勞的地方
If there's anything I can do,
儘管說
I'm at your service.
我們在找我妹妹
We're looking for my sister.
她的地址在這兒
She's staying at this address.
你能帶我們去那裡嗎?
Can you take us there?
老天爺
Oh, dear.
你們最好跟我來一趟
I think you'd better come with me.
小玲?
Lin.
阿文?
Wen.
你們不介意的話
If you don't mind,
我在外面等
I'll just wait outside.
介紹一下
Introduce me.
這是小玲  我的寶貝小妹
Oh. This is Lin, my baby sister.
我不是小孩了
歐·洛依
Roy O'Bannon.
幸會
Pleasure.
你沒對我說過你妹妹...
You never told me your sister was such a...
出水芙蓉一樣水靈啊!
beautiful lotus blossom.
這是你信里所說的美國朋友?
對
她說什麼?
What'd she say?
他長得蛮帥的
不準用漢語談論我
No talking about me in your native tongue.
你怎麼會在監獄裏?
Why are you in jail?
我跟蹤謀殺父親的兇手
I followed the man who murdered father.
然後呢?
And?
我跟蹤到他的住所
I found out where he live.
我溜進屋內  試圖殺了他
I snuck inside his house and tried to kill him.
找到殺父兇手是我的責任
It's my duty to find father's killer.
是我的  我答應了父親
No, it is mine! I'm the one who promised Father.
我是他唯一的兒子
But I'm his only son.
當你拋下我們遠赴美國時...
When you abandoned us for America...
父親就說他沒你這個兒子
Father said he had no son.
什麼?
What?
等等  時間到  過來
Whoa. Time out. Time out. Come here.
那個警探是書迷
The detective's a fan.
乾脆我跟他搞搞關係
Why don't I play the celebrity card?
再把她弄出來
We'll get her out that way.
-好嗎?  -好吧
- Okay? - Okay.
別擔心  我會救你出去
Don't worry. I'll get you out.
不會有事的
Everything's gonna be okay. In fact,
我把我的幸運撲克牌送你
I'm gonna give you my good-luck playing cards.
別太在意上面的裸女圖
just ignore the naked ladies.
阿文?
Wen!
你打開父親的盒子了嗎?
Have you opened Father's box?
還沒
Not yet.
她想趁羅朋閣下喝下午茶時
She tried to assassinate Lord Rathbone
刺殺羅朋閣下
whilst he was taking afternoon tea.
他是皇位的第十順位繼承人
He's 10th in line to the throne.
女皇最喜歡的堂弟
Her MaJesty's favorite cousin,
也是英國最頂尖的劍士
and the finest swordsman in England.
媒體大篇幅報導
So, of course, the press had a field day.
版面甚至比
The story actually knocked Jack the Ripper
開膛手傑克還大
off the front page.
亞瑟  小玲不是壞人
Artie, Lin is not a killer.
她只是個性感
She's just a really, really, really hot
又迷糊的中國女孩
confused Chinese girl.
要是我同意簽幾張簽名照
Maybe if I agreed to sign a few autographs
為英國的書迷開場座談會
and talk to some of my fans here in England.
參加慈善活動
Do some type of charity event,
能不能放她出來?
can we get her out that way?
恐怕那是不可能的
I'm afraid that's out of the question.
她會怎麼樣?
What will happen to my sister?
她會受審
She'll go to trial, probably be locked away
被關進精神療養所
in an institution for the criminally insane.
小報還封她為
The tabloids have already dubbed her
瘋子玲
"Loony Lin".
我覺得滿帖切的
I thought it was rather catchy.
就當時而言
At the time.
你知不知道
Do you have any notion what would happen
有人看到我們在一起就完了
if we were to be seen together?
從你回來到現在
Since your return,
我還沒看到玉璽呢
I have yet to lay eyes on the Imperial Seal.
我明天在郊外別墅
I'm hosting a Jubilee ball
舉辦慶祝舞會
at my country estate tomorrow.
午夜到馬廄來
Be at the stables at midnight.
依約定  這是憑據
As requested, a token of my esteem.
你該下車了
This is where you get out.
希望你我在各自繼承王位後
I hope there will be more trust between us
能加深對彼此的信任
when I'm emperor and you are the new king.
姜  是白金漢宮吔
Wow. Buckingham Palace. Look at that,
瞧  女皇就住那裡
Chon. That's where the queen lives.
看看這傢伙
Hey, look at this guy.
他是皇家侍衛
He's a royal guard.
他的工作很重要
He has a very important Job.
我以前就象他一樣
I used to be just like him.
不  他們和你完全不一樣
No, they're nothing like you.
他們只是為了吸引遊客
They're a tourist attraction.
你能向他們做鬼臉  侮辱他們
You can make faces at them, insult them,
而他們連動都不能動
and they can't move a muscle.
-瞧我的  -洛依
- Here. Watch this. - Roy.
沒關係的
No, It's okay.
老兄  你鞋帶鬆了
Hey, buddy, your shoes are untied.
你頭頂上的鳥巢真大啊
That is the biggest damn beaver I have ever seen.
洛依  別鬧了
Roy, stop it.
女皇  快看  女皇!
The queen! Look, The queen!
她裸奔過來了!
She's mooning us!
他差點就上當了
He almost went for that.
我來自美國  你可能聽說過
My friend and I just came over from America.
我們打贏了
You might have heard of it.
你們這個微小的國家
We run your Jerkwater country.
拜託  你打算忍受這一切?
Come on, you gonna take that from a colonial?
洛依  別鬧了
Roy, stop it.
想你一定很會耍老千吧
I bet you are one hell of a damn poker player.
我沒有惡意
No hard feelings.
他們不能這樣的
They can't do that!
他們不允許打人的
They don't allow do that!
你不該碰他的
Shouldn't have touched him.
一邊去  小鬼
You scram, you little punk.
我警局有朋友
I've got friends at Scotland Yard.
會讓你怕我的
I'll give you up in a heartbeat.
找回你的表了?
You get your watch back?
別管我的表  快走開
Don't worry about my watch. Go on.
-那是個假貨  -什麼假貨?
- It's a knockoff. - What are you talking about?
我叔叔從林肯總統身上偷來的
My uncle stole this watch from President Lincoln.
那是無價的傳家寶
It's a priceless family heirloom.
當鋪老闆可不是這麼說的
Not according to the pawnbroker.
你不該偷東西的
You should not steal.
我若不偷  就沒東西吃
If I don't steal, I don't eat.
對了  能告訴我是
By the way, Who showed you how to do
誰教你那樣打架的嗎?
all that kicking and punching?
我父親
My father.
聽說過嗎?  父母!
Have you ever heard of those? They're parents.
我們是有父母疼愛的
We have parents love us.
你沒有  因為你是個小孤兒
You Don't cause you're a little orphan.
快走開  你真礙眼
Now, go on. You're cramping our style.
這是什麼鳥國家啊
Oh, this country blows.
需要地方落腳嗎?
You need a place to stay?
進來暖暖吧
Come on in and warm your dogs.
闖入這種地方
You can get into a lot of trouble
會惹上麻煩的
breaking into a place like this.
話又說回來了  幹得好
That being said, well done.
你吃了最後一個巧克力
You just ate the last chocolate.
沒錯  人不為己天誅地滅
Course I did. You gotta look out for number one.
我可以習慣這一切
I could really get used to this.
過着鄉紳的生活
Living the life of a country gentleman.
也許再畫幾幅畫
Maybe doing a little painting.
讓小玲在花園裡跟孩子玩耍
Let Lin play in the garden with the children.
維拉  查克和戴維
Vera, Chuck, and Dave.
誰是小玲?
Who's Lin?
小玲是我所見過最美的女人
Lin's the most beautiful woman l've ever met.
她將是歐氏莊園的女主人
She's gonna be the savior of the house of O'Bannon.
姜  看看我的衣服怎麼樣?
Chon, check out the threads.
我就差腳邊蜷伏一隻
All I'm missing is the
忠心的獵犬了
loyal hound curled at my feet.
咱們這是在浪費時間
We are wasting time.
必須先找到羅朋
We must find Rathbone.
你以為我在做什麼?
What do you think l've been doing?
僅僅是坐着享用美酒嗎?
Sitting here drinking expensive hooch?
小弟  倒酒
Boy, refill.
我想出了一個計劃
L've been working on a plan.
別把白蘭地灑出來了
Now... Whoa. Don't slosh the brandy.
-那會搞砸氣氛的  -省省吧
- It messes with the bouquet. - Sod off.
我在教你生活竅門
I'm trying to teach you a skill set.
幫你擺脫混街頭的生活
Help get you off the street.
-當酒保很賺錢的  -洛依
- Bartenders make big bucks. - Roy!
計劃  謝謝你  姜
The plan. Thank you, Chon.
我想要是我們能找到玉璽
If we find the seal...
就能證明羅朋殺了你爸
we can prove Rathbone killed your dad.
讚歎吧
It's the old Hail Mary play.
我還有個挖地道的圖
I also have a version where we dig a tunnel.
天吶!  彈射器
Bloody catapult. Jesus Christ!
-不需要彈射器  -誰問你啦?
- You Don't need a catapult! - Who asked you?
大人說話  小孩別插嘴
You don't interrupt grown-ups when they're talking.
羅朋閣下邀請
"Lord Nelson Rathbone requests
您和您的同伴
the pleasure of your company
參加女皇即位
at the Jubilee ball in honor
五十周年慶祝舞會
of Her MaJesty's 50th year on the throne."
聽起來不錯
Sounds good.
可那騙不了警衛
It doesn't address security.
他們當然不會讓我們就這樣進去
They're not gonna let Chon and I waltz into the castle.
你們只需要改裝一下
All you need is a proper disguise.
我喜歡改裝
I do like a good disguise.
我看起來像笨蛋
I look like a fool.
什麼?  你是印度大君
What? You're a maharaja.
是印度的皇室
That's Indian royalty.
但我是中國人
But I'm Chinese.
看起來差不多
It's the same thing.
來  搖一下你的腦袋
Bob your head a little bit.
這讓你更有印度皇室的味道
Gives you more of a India-royalty flavor.
很好  好耶  好耶
That's good. Good show, good show.
好耶  好耶
Good show, good show.
-再見  -再見
- Cheerio, cheerio. - Cheerio, cheerio.
我們見到羅朋時該怎麼辦?
What do we do when we see Rathbone?
殺了他
Kill him.
不行  拜託
No, okay? No!
不行  你得有點禮貌
You're gonna be civil,
我們還沒找到玉璽啊
cause we Don't have the seal.
沒玉璽  沒小玲
No seal. No Lin.
也沒家族榮譽  懂嗎?
No family honor. Okay?
冷靜點  這樣看起來不錯
Be cool. Okay, we look great.
去參加宴會吧
Let's enjoy this party.
你要去哪兒?
Whoa. What are you doing?
進去啊  聽說這裡鬧鬼
I'm going inside. They said the place is haunting
不  你是馬夫
No, You're the harness man.
你得待在馬車裡
Which mean you get back at the carriage.
隨時待命
You wait in case we need to make a quick getaway.
快去  要盡忠職守
Go on. Man your post.
不能總是想什麼有什麼
You don't always get what you want.
你幹什麼對那孩子這麼凶?
Why are you so mean to that boy?
我在他身上看到自己的影子
I see a lot of myself in that kid.
那讓我很火大  走吧
It's kind of freaking me out. Come on.
先生  您的大名
Your name, please, sir.
我好宣布您的到來
So I can announce you.
夏洛克...  福爾摩斯
Sherlock... Holmes.
夏洛克·福爾摩斯
Sherlock Holmes.
王公閣下
Which province do you represent,
您所代表的省份是?
Your Highness?
內華達
Nevada.
請允許我介紹夏洛克·福爾摩斯少將
May I present Major General Sherlock Holmes
與內華達省大君閣下
and His Highness, the maharaja of Nevada.
今晚的警衛戒備
How are the security arrangements
沒問題吧?
this evening respect?
一切都很順利
Oh, everything seems to be
閣下
going swimmingly, my Lord.
容我直言
And if I may say so...
能為您執行警衛工作真是榮幸
it is an honor to guard Your Lordship tonight.
我謹代表警局全體發言
I speak for all of us at Scotland Yard when I say that
不論您離王位有多遠
no matter how far you are from the throne.
您都是我們心目中第一繼承人
You'll always be number one in our hearts.
計劃是這樣的
Okay, here's the plan.
我們先吃點東西
We're gonna get a little chow.
再溜出去
Then we're gonna sneak out of here.
-找玉璽  -好
- Start looking for that seal. - Okay.
先生  嘗嘗葡萄乾布丁嗎?
Spotted Dick, sir?
啥東西?
What?
葡萄乾布丁
Spotted Dick.
你看這傢伙
Can you believe this guy?
我想吃點東西
I'm trying to get something to eat.
他卻想占我便宜
He's asking me if I got the clap.
我想他是問你要不要吃東西
I think he's offering you food.
葡萄乾布丁
Oh. Spotted Dick.
不用了
Oh, no. I think I'll pass.
我不愛吃甜點
I'm not really a dessert man.
我朋友可能會想吃
Perhaps my friend might like some Spotted Dick.
我想來點這種香腸
I might try one of these sausages.
煙熏腸
A little smoky Joe.
真好吃
Mmm! This is good!
我聽說過英國食物很糟糕
I thought the food here was supposed to suck.
這羊雜腸是剛從蘇格蘭運來的
The haggis is fresh from Scotland, sir.
用最好的羊膀胱製成
It's made from the finest sheeps bladders.
我需要些威士忌漱漱口
I'm gonna get some whiskey and wash my mouth out.
你該試試鵪鶉肉
You should try the quail.
我今早自己打獵打來的
I shot them myself this morning.
您好  閣下
How do you do, Your Lordship?
很好  謝謝你
Very well, thank you.
我對內華達省不太熟
I'm not acquainted with the Nevada province.
81年以後就沒去過印度了
But I haven't been to India since 81.
大多時候都待在東方
I spent most of my time in the Orient.
我聽說您剛從中國回來
I hear you've just returned from China.
你消息很靈通  大君
You are well-informed, maharaja.
我夢想中國能跟隨印度的腳步
It is my dream that the Chinese people
有一天能納入大英國版圖
will follow India's example and one day embrace British rule.
中國人很驕傲
The Chinese are very proud.
他們把家族  榮譽放第一位
They place family and honor above all else.
我相信我們能打破那些成規
Well, I'm sure we can break them of that.
抱歉  我還有事
If you'll excuse me, I have a matter to attend to.
期待再相會
Until we meet again.
要有耐心  我很以你為傲
Patience. I'm proud of you, Chon.
我們得找到玉璽
We must find the seal.
你看到什麼了?
What do you see?
他拿出一支漂亮的龍鑰匙
He just pulled a fancy dragon key out of his desk.
那是我父親的  我要為他報仇
That was my father's, I must avenge his honor.
別急  老大
Hey, slow down, tiger. Slow down.
別動不動就想報仇
Quit going all Chinese on me.
他人呢?
Where is he?
記得你的七巧盒吧  耐心
Damn it. Remember your puzzle box. Patience.
這裡沒窗戶
Okay, there are no windows.
只有一扇門
We just came in through the only doorway.
那只有一個解釋
That leaves one explanation.
在洛依大戰木乃伊里
Remember in "Roy O'Bannon vs. The Mummy"
我追殭屍王
how the zombie king got away
追到法老陵墓中?
when I chased him into the pharaoh's tomb?
獅身人面像下有秘密通道
There's a secret passageway behind the sphinx.
這裡一定有個按鈕或翹桿
There's gotta be a lever or a button over here.
幫我把東西拿起來
Help me lift some stuff up.
洛依  那幅畫  它在看我
Roy! The painting. It's looking at me.
你看!
Look!
是啊  它也在看着我啊
Oh, yeah. Looks like It's looking at me. That's great.
不  是真的眼睛  會動的
No, real eyes. Moving!
那個小孩騙到你了  對吧?
That kid got to you, didn't he?
真是的  這裡不是鬼屋
Unbelievable! We're not in a haunted house.
那只是畫家的一種繪畫技巧
That's a technique that an artist uses.
被稱為  擬真眼神
"Ubiquitous gaze" or "pursuant eyes" is the technical term.
我告訴你  那沒什麼啦
It's unnerving, though. I'll give you that.
洛依  那些眼睛  快看
Roy. Now, those eyes. Look!
隨便你啦
Whatever you say, Chon.
讓我看看你有什麼好料  羅朋
Let's see what you got here, Rathbone.
洛依!
Roy!
怎麼  這回是雕像會動了?
What, Chon? Are the statues moving now?
洛依!
Roy!
該死  你的鬼叫讓我無法思考
I can't hear myself think with you shouting at me.
姜
Chon?
姜  姜?
Chon? Chon?
真受夠了
This is ridiculous.
姜  你想玩躲迷藏
If you want to act like a child and play games...
去找別人吧
then find someone else.
我很認真在工作
cause I take this stuff seriously.
我有任務在身
I'm here to work. I'm on a mission.
姜?
Chon?
好吧  姜
Okay, Chon.
好  要玩就來玩吧
Okay, you little Chinese otter. Let's play.
姜  有妖怪!
Chon, demons!
她為我而奮戰
She's gonna fight my battles for me.
來  我們走吧
Come on. Let's go.
什麼  你要去哪兒?
What? What are you doing?
搞變態  我喜歡
It's kinky. I like it.
你看看
Wow! Look at this.
這房間似乎不太一樣了
Wait. There's something different about this room.
我們走
Let's go!
-阿文!  -姜  老天!  -小玲!
- Wen! - Chon, for God's sakes. - Lin
-他終於出現了  -我找到了
- Now he shows up. - I found it.
姜  你不想聽我說嗎?
Wait. Do you want to hear?
玉璽不見了
The seal's gone.
小玲
Lin.
洛依
Roy!
我們還會回來嗎?
Are we gonna come back?
洛依
Roy!
你一定要老是這樣嗎?
Must you keep doing that?
有人教我要來去無影蹤
I was taught not to be seen or heard.
玉璽
The seal.
我是個守信用的人
I am a man of my word.
我還記得小時候曾看着我哥
I remember watching my brother
把玩這東西  象個孩子的玩具
play with this like a baby rattle.
我想碰它...
When I'd try to touch it...
卻被皇太后打
the dowager empress beat me.
你可悲的童年
No doubt your deprived childhood
造就了今日的你
made you into the man you are today.
烏義?
Wu Chow.
什麼?
Wu who?
皇帝的混蛋弟弟
He is the emperor's bastard brother.
被逐出皇宮
He was banished from the Forbidden City
因為他想偷玉璽
for trying to steal the Imperial Seal.
我們的父親驅逐了他
Our father caught him.
他誓言要奪回皇位
He vowed to return to claim the emperor's throne.
就這傢伙?
This guy?
我想一切都安排好了吧
I'll assume everything has been arranged as discussed.
別擔心
You have nothing to worry about.
全都搞定了
It's all in place.
那鑽石跟猴子屁股一樣大
That diamond is as big as a damn monkey's paw.
洛依  你想都別想
Roy. Don't even think about it.
我只是在讚歎
I'm just admiring the craftsmanship, Chon.
現在  我們的合作圓滿達成
So for now, our business is completed.
小玲呢?
Where's Lin?!
逮到你了
Gotcha!
人不為己  天誅地滅
just looking out for number one.
不!
No!
那小子拿走玉璽了!
The kid got the seal!
姜!
Chon!
卡住了
It's stuck.
小玲!
Lin!
來
come
快  你做得到
Go! You can do it!
她成功了  她成功了
She's got it. She's got it!
洛依  快點!
Roy! Come on!
姜
Chon, what in our history together
你憑什麼以為我會飛檐走壁?
makes you think I'm capable of something like that?
-洛依!  -我做不到
- Roy! - I can't do that!
快點!
Hurry up!
等等  有更好的辦法
Wait. There's a better way.
-小心  慢一點!  -我這是猛虎出閘!
- Slow down! - I'm a bat out of hell!
何況  我不知道剎車在哪裡
Besides, I don't know where the brake is.
什麼?
What?
小心!
Look out!
老兄  慢一點
Slow down, buddy.
放鬆  別緊張
Relax, relax.
這裡很平坦
Smooth sailing from here.
對  就是這兩個人攻擊我
Yes, these are the men who attacked me.
恐怕他們已經跑了
I'm afraid the assailants have temporarily eluded us,
閣下
my Lord.
也許你能解釋
Perhaps you could explain to me
瘋子玲是如何
how Loony Lin managed to escape
在警方嚴密監視下
from the confines of Scotland Yard under the watch
逃離監獄的?
of the most respected police force in the world.
當然  真是太非同尋常了
Yes, of course. It's absolutely fascinating.
她用一副色情撲克牌
She picked the lock
把鎖給打開
using a deck of rather risque playing cards.
然後用抹布和一堆偷來的內衣
Then scaled the walls with a mop, a fork...
翻過牆去
and various pilfered undergarments.
你得承認中國人真是聰明
You've got to hand it to the Chinese.
他們足智多謀  心靈手巧  不是嗎?
They're awfully ingenious, Lord, aren't they?
你也太無能了吧
Does your incompetence know no bounds?!
我在哪裡?
Where am I?
小玲
Lin!
我不認識這些女人
I don't even know these women.
小玲  你在這裡幹什麼?
Lin, what are you doing here?
老天啊
Oh, Lord.
想試試第37頁的姿勢嗎?
Do you want to try the position on page 37?
過來  你這隻小綿羊
Come here, you little minx.
這是怎麼回事?
What?
-你沒事吧?  -我有事
- You okay? - No, I'm not okay.
我剛被綿羊性侵害
L've just been violated by a barnyard animal.
是誰在路中間
Who would leave a pile of stones
堆了一堆石頭?
in the middle of the field?
不知道  這些人都瘋了
I don't know, Chon. These people are nuts.
走吧
Come on.
我能不能告訴你一件事?
Can I tell you something?
什麼事?
What?
這趟冒險之旅真棒
This is a hell of a damn adventure we're on.
我跟你在一起很愉快
I'm having an absolute ball with you.
我也是
Me too.
好  伸出大拇指  印度大君
Here we go. Get your thumb out, maharaja.
-為什麼?  -過來
- Why? - Get over here.
抱歉
Excuse me!
小玲?
- Lin! - Lin!
肩膀有點僵硬
My shoulder's getting a little tight.
這是你頭一回來英國吧?
This is your first time in England, isn't it?
你怎麼認得路  太神奇了?
How do you know your way around? It's incredible.
我的方向感很好
I always had a good sense of direction.
我完全同意
You can say that again.
真希望那傢伙也一樣
I wish we could say the same about you-know-who.
我曾送他上山
I once sent him over a mountain range.
他卻迷路了
He was lost forever.
有次我送他過長城
One time, I sent him over the Great Wall.
-他就迷了三天路  -三天?
- He was lost for three days. - Three days?!
我們有好多共同的話題
Oh, gosh, we got a lot in common.
我沒遇過像你一樣的人
L've never met anybody like you, Roy.
真的?  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
能不能說句冒昧的話?
Hey, can I tell you something without you getting offended?
什麼?
What?
你的身材真棒
You have a great body.
好了  我說了  全說出來了
There. I said it. It's out in the open.
-你一定常運動  -我?
- You must work out. - Me?
抱歉
Excuse me.
姜  你幹什麼?
Chon, what are you doing?
我不喜歡坐后座
I don't like the backseat.
我會暈車  頭昏
Makes me sick. Dizzy.
懷特查珀爾
Whitechapel.
看來是個好地方
This looks like a nice enough neighborhood.
什麼是長靴貓?
What is Puss and Boots?
廉價旅館
It's a boardinghouse. Some of the sailors
船上水手特別推薦的
on the ship coming over recommended it.
我妹妹不能住這裡
I won't let my sister stay here.
那我們住哪裡?
What are we supposed to do?
去住大飯店?
Check in to the Savoy?
我們會被逮到的
We'll get arrested before we get to our room.
我不介意住這裡
I don't mind this place.
看吧  她可開通多了
See? She's a little open-minded.
我知道這很瘋狂  才剛認識...
I know this sounds crazy cause I just met her...
但我愛上了她
but I think I'm falling for her.
就是她了
I think She's the one.
洛依  她是我的小妹
Roy, She's my baby sister.
我知道  感謝上帝
I know she is. Thank God!
這是我唯一的機會
That's the only chance l've got.
聽着  我準備發動
I'm getting ready to launch a little thing
一見鍾情大作戰
called "Operation, Sweep Her Off Her Feet."
你可以當我的說客  行嗎?
You're in a position to talk me up.
拜託  兄弟
Can I count on you? Please, buddy,
我從沒求過你
I've never asked you for anything.
當然  我會跟她說實話
Sure, Roy. I'll tell her the truth.
這次幫我打打圓場
Don't get hung up on the truth.
說說好話
Feel free to smooth out your old pal's rough edges.
我愛你  兄弟
I love you, buddy.
小玲
Lin.
過來
Come.
坐
Sit.
親愛的  想玩嗎?
Hello, love. Fancy a tumble?
這要是在兩天前
Oh! Where were you two days ago?
我立刻就上
I would have bedded you in a second.
現在我已經變了
Now you're looking at a changed man.
我要為某個特別的人守身
I'm sort of saving myself for someone special.
我給你打折
I'll give you a discount.
那是我聽過
That's the most romantic thing
最浪漫的話語了
any woman's ever said to me.
你最好趁我沒改變心意前離開
You better go, You better go
快走
before we lose control. Go!
要是你改變主意...
If you change your mind...
小玲  父親說過  當你夫婿的條件
Our father would talk about the right man for you.
必須身體強健  勇敢
He must be strong, courageous...
-也要是個好父親  -就像洛依一樣
-and a good father. - Like Roy.
不是像洛依那樣
Not like Roy.
你不像我一樣了解他
You don't know him like I do.
他有很多壞習慣
He has many bad habits.
比如說?
Such as?
他喝酒  抽煙又賭博
He drinks, smokes, and he gambles.
你說這幹什麼?
Chon, where are you going with this?
他為了錢陪女人睡覺
He sleeps with women for money.
洛依不會的
Roy don't do that.
我了解他的內心
I can see inside him.
他有副好心腸
He has a good heart.
沒錯
That's right.
他的蝌蚪根本不會游泳
His salmon don't swim upstream.
他只會打空包彈
He shoots blanks.
小玲  他不值得信任
Lin, he cannot be trusted.
你怎能這麼說?
How could you say that?
你是他的朋友
You're his friend.
是啊  算吧
Yeah, sort of.
洛依是那種
Roy is the type of a friend
你不會介紹給朋友
you'd never introduce to your other friends
或帶回家的朋友
or bring home to your family.
他老愛說謊
He never speak the truth.
知道我怎麼叫他嗎?
You know what I call him?
不是歐·洛依  是瞎掰王·洛依
Not Roy O'Bannon. Roy O'Baloney.
我不在乎
I don't care.
小玲  我不準
Lin, I forbid it.
你不是我父親
You are not my father.
洛依  你在這裡啊
Roy, there you are.
需要什麼嗎?
You need anything? Buddy.
我需要的是  別來煩我
A whole lot of "leave me alone".
怎麼了?
What's wrong?
沒什麼  起床的時候沒注意
Nothing. I woke up on the wrong side of the bed.
後背擰了  有點痛
I feel a little pain in my back
好像有人從背後捅了我一刀
like someone put a knife there.
我很好  不用擔心我
I'm okay. Don't worry about me.
洛依
Roy!
你倒提醒了我
That actually reminds me of a trick.
看過這招嗎?
You ever seen this one?!
或是這招?
or this one?
你以為會兩下拳腳功夫
You think you're so cool with your karate
就有什麼了不起
and your childlike reflexes.
洛依  你還好吧?
Roy, you okay?
看看你
Look at you.
你真的叫我瞎掰王·洛依?
Do you really call me Roy Baloney?
洛依  你不明白
Roy, you don't understand.
你打碎了我的七巧盒
You just smashed my puzzle box.
我永遠猜不透它的玄機了
I'll never figure out my message.
洛依
Roy.
走開
Go.
你我已形同陌路
You're dead to me.
我不認識什麼姜文
I don't know a Chon Wen.
-搞什麼啊?  -你好  洛依
- What? - Hi, Roy.
誰最愛你啊  寶貝?
Who loves you, baby?
-這招不壞  -洛依
- Nice try, Chon. - Roy.
對不起
I'm sorry.
再來一次  你就死定了
You do that again, and you're a dead man.
枕頭大戰!
Pillow fight!
-我是瞎掰王·洛依!  -沒錯!
- I am Roy Baloney! - Yes!
-我是超級瞎掰王!  -沒錯!
- I'm full of it! - You are!
洛依?
Roy?
小玲
Lin!
這是他的主意
It was his idea.
-姜!  -穿衣服!
- Chon! - Clothes!
真是散步的好夜晚
Nice night for a walk.
去死吧  你個窩囊廢
You loser
-小玲  -玲
-Lin! - Lin!
-你在這裡!  -你在幹什麼?
- There you are! - What are you doing?
開膛手還逍遙法外呢!
Don't you know there's a serial killer on the loose?
算了
Forget it.
-這些人是誰?  -拳匪
- Who the hell are these guys? - Boxers.
幹嘛找上我們?
What do they want with us?
他們是我的人
They're with me.
我想我們需要談談
I think we need to have a little chat.
姜文...
Chon Wen...
違抗皇命的人
the man who can fight an emperor.
皇上真不該饒你一命
The emperor should never have his burial knife.
我明白了
I see.
你還是我堂哥的走狗
You're still my brother's lapdog.
我不是為他來此
I'm here not for him.
我是為了我父親
I'm here for my father.
當然了
Of course you are.
就是我這把匕首刺進他心臟
It was my dagger that plunged into his heart.
這上面還沾有他的血呢
It's still crusted with his blood.
我知道那小鬼拿走了玉璽
I know the boy has the seal.
他人呢?
Where is he?
我們不知道  這是實話
We Don't know. That's the truth.
真的不知道
We don't know.
你要幹什麼?
What are you doing?
別降了  放她下來!
No stop, put her down!
放她下來  快放她下來!
Put her down! Put her down!
不然你要怎樣?
Or what, Mr. O'Bannon?
你要海扁我一頓嗎?
Are you gonna kick my ass?
我看過你那些荒謬的小說
L've read all about your ridiculous exploits.
徒手殺木乃伊...
I mean, just... how does it feel
是什麼感覺?
to kill a mummy with your bare hands?
只有沒教養的粗人
Only a nation of uneducated rednecks
才會喜歡那種爛小說
would be amused by such cowboy drivel.
幹嘛做人身攻擊啊?
Easy, What's with the personal attacks?
你有聽到我批評你慘白的臉色
You Don't see me making any comments
或是你令人討厭的腔調
about your pasty complexion or your snotty accent
還有骯髒  噁心的性愛大全
or even your filthy, smutty sex books.
沒錯  我看過你的書了  噁心
Yeah, I saw your book. It disgusted me.
幹什麼老打頭啊?
Oh, why is it always the head with you people?!
等等!  住手!  等等!
Hold it! Stop! Hold it! just hold it!
我們這是在幹嘛
What are we doing here?
你們看看?
Guys, look at this.
這跟動物沒兩樣嘛
We're acting like animals.
為了什麼  就為了玉璽?
over what? Some seal?
玉璽代表皇帝的權力
The seal represents imperial power.
我將用它來統合皇帝的敵人
I will use it to unite the emperor's enemies
進攻紫禁城
and storm the Forbidden City.
你有什麼好處?
What's in it for you?
你正看着未來的英國國王
You're looking at the future king of England.
你是第二十順位的繼承人吧?
You're, like, 20th in line to the throne.
第十
10th.
我朋友正打算用簡單的
But my friend is about to change all that
消去法來改變這一切
by simple process of elimination.
這是機關槍
It's called a machine gun.
一分鐘可射出二百發子彈
The first of its kind, it fires 200 rounds a minute.
這是英國發明的里程碑
Testament to British ingenuity.
你負責偷玉璽
Oh, so you steal the seal,
你負責幹掉九個皇族?
and then you knock off nine royals?
你的差事比較爛
You got the short end of that stick, my friend.
把他們沉到河裡去
Dump them in the river.
你帶她去哪?
Where are you taking her?
去創造歷史
To make history.
我已經能看到新聞頭條
I can already see the headlines.
舉國哀悼瘋子玲屠殺皇室
"Nation mourns as Loony Lin massacres royal family."
你得保證會找到玉璽
I need your assurance that you will find the seal.
別擔心
Don't concern yourself.
我的人正在找
My men are scouring the city.
他們最好能找到
You better pray they find it.
不然我們的約定就失效
or our agreement is over,
而你也永遠不能戴上皇冠
and you will never get the crown.
姜  我得向你坦白
Chon, I got a confession to make.
你愛我妹妹
You are in love with my sister.
那是真的
Well, that, but...
但我並沒有把錢都拿去炒股票
I didn't lose all the money on the zeppelins.
沒有嗎?
No?
大部分我都拿去印洛依的小說
Nah. I blew most of it on the Roy O'Bannon novels.
我寫的
I wrote them.
那些是塞奇·麥卡利斯特寫的
No, Sage McCallister wrote them.
沒錯
That's what I'm saying, buddy.
我就是塞奇·麥卡利斯特
I'm Sage McCallister.
那些謊言都是你寫的?
You wrote those lies?
我不太知恥
I've always had low self-esteem.
印了多少本?
How many books did you print?
我印了一百萬本
I self-published probably a million copies.
年度印刷量僅次於聖經
We were actually second to the Bible that year.
你...
Oh, you...
我真是個
I guess I'm just about the worst friend
最糟糕的朋友
a guy could ask for.
-不  你是個好朋友  -謝謝你
- No, you're a good friend. - Thank you.
你若真愛小玲
If you really love Lin,
我不會阻止你
I won't stand in the way.
真的?
Really?
但你若敢傷她的心
But if you break her heart,
我就打斷你的腿
I'll break your legs.
很公平
That's fair.
生死之交  姜
Well, friends to the end, Chon...
這回死定了
and this is the end.
姜  有計劃嗎?
Chon, you got a plan?
你不會正好有吧?
You wouldn't happen to have a plan, would you?
有
Yes.
-需要我幫忙嗎?  -不用
- Anything I can do? - No.
很好
Good.
麻煩事就交給你了
I'll let you do the heavy lifting, then.
快  快叫人來幫忙
Hurry! Get someone to help
姜  快點!
Chon, hurry.
Chon! Chon, hurry! Hurry!
姜!
Roy!
來了!
Coming!
姜!
Chon!
把他抓起來
Take him!
真臟  臟死了!  受不了了!
The water's so dirty! No! No! It's dirty! No!
淹死我吧
just go ahead and drown me.
我無所謂了
I don't care anymore.
姜!
Chon!
洛依!
Roy!
你死去哪了?
上面挺忙的
真是的
你要有耐心
去跟我褲管里的海鰻說吧
你們這身打扮真荒唐
You look ridiculous.
我覺得滿好的
I think we look good.
我真的抗議你們非法入侵
I really must protest this intrusion.
全倫敦的警察
Every bobby in London is out
都在找你們
scouring the streets for you two.
-你喝酒了?
-Have you been drinking? - I always drink
失業的時候當然要喝酒
when my employment's been terminated.
他們解僱了你?
They fired you?
是羅朋下的決定
Lord Rathbone saw to that.
對不起
I'm sorry.
這不要緊
It's of no consequence.
反正我本來就不想當警探
I never wanted to be an inspector in the first place.
那是我父親的意思
It was my father's idea.
我一直都想當作家
I always wanted to be a writer.
理解
Yeah.
我們需要你幫忙
Artie, we need your help.
羅朋帶走小玲
Rathbone has taken Lin.
他會屠殺皇室
He's gonna kill the royal family
繼承王位
and he's gonna assume the throne.
你們有證據支持
Do you have any evidence to support
這不合理的論斷嗎?
these preposterous allegations?
我們有這個  是那個男孩的
We have this. It's the boy's.
用你的技巧  查出他在哪
Use your technique. Tell us where he is.
石蠟  真有趣
Paraffin wax, most interesting.
那個死小孩躲在教堂里
He's at a church. The little punk's hiding in a church.
不  不
No, no, no.
這不是蠟燭的蠟
It's not candle wax.
有了
I have it.
塔索蠟像館
這支沒用  別擔心  你行的
Don't worry. You'll get it.
-你們在幹什麼?  -他在開鎖
- What are you doing? - He's picking the lock.
那就快點啊!
Well, hurry up!
姜  拜託
Chon, please! Please.
這是很繁瑣的過程
It's a very meticulous process.
讓阿蒂去做
Let Artie do his Job.
這近乎藝術
It's almost an art form.
像外科手術一樣精密
It takes the precision of a surgeon.
一切都要精準無比
You have to be so precise.
再塞一支進去
Maybe if we Jam another one in there.
那也有用
That works, too.
只是不夠細膩
Lacks a certain finesse.
分開行動
All right, Let's split up.
搞什麼...
What the...
我要扭斷你的脖子  過來
I am gonna break your neck, Come here.
你那邊怎麼樣?
How is you going?
-你那邊怎麼樣?  -解開那繩子
- How is you going?  - Put me down first
瞧瞧這是誰
Looky here.
-出來  東西呢?  -什麼?
- Come on, where is it? - What?
你知道我說的是什麼
You know what I'm talking about.
別裝傻了  給我表
Don't give me that "what."
這是什麼?
What do we got here?
找到了
Oh, yes.
你不介意我把它拿回來吧
You Don't mind if I take this back, do you?
快走  滾出去!
Go on. Get out of here. Go!
洛依
Roy?
我找到了
I got it.
把玉璽給我
Give me the seal.
把玉璽給我!
Give me the seal!
好了  都散開
All right, spread out!
在那邊
Through there!
快走
Let's go.
沒戲唱了
The gig's up.
我們該怎麼辦?
So, what are we gonna do?
快點  想啊
Come on, think!
我不想進英國監獄
I'm not going to an English prison.
我這一頭金黃的秀髮
With my feathery blond hair
姜這健壯的身體
and Chon's athletic build,
我們肯定會被玩爆
they'll try to make us the belle of the ball.
想都別想  我不回去
Forget it. I'm not going back.
至少我們可以在警局裡
Well, at least we'll get a good view
看到漂亮的煙火秀
of the fireworks from Scotland Yard.
-煙火秀?  - 是的
- Fireworks? - Yeah.
午夜時  泰晤士河上的船隻
At midnight, they're launching this huge display
會施放壯麗的煙火
from a flotilla of barges on the Thames.
慶祝女皇即位五十周年
It's the official kickoff to the Queen's Jubilee.
皇室成員會到場嗎?
Is the royal family gonna be there?
他們會在皇宮陽台上
They're gonna be viewing the spectacle
觀賞那壯觀的場面
from a balcony overlooking the river.
他在船上裝了機關槍
He's got a machine gun on the barge.
沒錯
Yes.
先生們迷路了嗎?
You gents lost your way?
你一定知道怎麼出去
Kid, tell me you got a way out.
幹得漂亮  小鬼
Nice move, kid.
你幹嘛回來?
So why did you come back?
你為何放棄玉璽?
Why did you give up the seal?
因為我是個笨蛋
Cause I'm a fool.
我想我也是個笨蛋吧
Guess I'm a fool, too.
手伸過來  笨蛋
Well, put her there, fool.
-你叫什麼名字?  -卓別林
- I never got your name. - Name's Chaplin
查理·卓別林
Charlie Chaplin.
你長大了
把她殺了
煙火開始的時候
把她的屍體放在大炮的旁邊
-借過  -請讓一讓
- Excuse me. - Excuse me. please!
你去警告皇室
You warn the royal family.
我去救小玲
I'll save Lin.
你怎麼救?
How on earth are you gonna do that?
你沒事吧?
You okay?
我剛救了你!
I just saved you!
誰讓你來這麼晚!
You were late!
什麼?
What?!
尼爾森?
Nelson?
你為何躲在後面?
Why are you hiding yourself back there?
我不該阻礙您觀賞煙火
I shouldn't like to impede your view,
女王殿下
Your Highness.
那不合情理  這都是你辛苦的結果
Nonsense. You arranged all this.
你應該有前排的位置
You should have a front-row view.
很抱歉  我必須拒絕
I regret that, uh, respectfully I must decline.
我得仔細監看典禮進行
I need to keep a good eye on proceedings.
尼爾森  你真是太能幹了
Nelson, you've outdone yourself.
結尾會更精彩
Wait till you see the finale.
我們一定沒辦法的
This is hopeless.
我們過不了警衛那關的
We're not gonna get past the guards.
這樣是不行  來吧
Well, not with that attitude we won't.
一定有辦法過去
Come on, Artie. There's got to be a way.
總會有辦法
There's always.
阿文!
Chon!
小玲!
Lin!
我們得跳過去
We got to jump it!
烏義!
Wu Chow!
別跑  羅朋
Hold it right there, Rathboner.
這樣落跑
I'm guessing by your hasty retreat
你肯定還是第二十順位
that you're still 20th in line for the throne.
是第十
10th.
多伊爾督察  逮捕這個人
Inspector Doyle, arrest this man.
他手上有槍
He's got a gun!
快一點
Come on!
-你還好吧?  -怎麼回事?
- You okay? - What happened?
羅朋用槍射傷了他
Rathbone nailed Artie with a little sissy gun.
我來照顧他  你們兩個去追
I'll look after him. You two go.
快去!
Go!
為了父親
For Father.
為了姜他老爸
For Old Man Wen.
我的幸運撲克牌
Oh, my lucky playing cards.
小心點
Be careful.
叫羅朋小心點吧
Tell Rathbone to be careful.
洛依  我們走
Roy, let's go.
換一支大管一點的槍吧!
You're gonna need a bigger gun!
-你看到他了?  -沒
- You see him? - No.
出來啊  羅朋!
Show your face, Rathbone!
我要把他碎屍萬段
I'm gonna tear this guy apart.
洛依  你找這邊  我找那邊
Roy, you go this way. I'll go that way.
分開  這主意不好吧?
Split up? I don't know if That's a good idea.
沒事
It's okay.
他不在這上面
He's not up here.
洛依  繼續找
Roy, keep going.
到底在哪裡?
Aw, come on, Roy.
羅朋
Hey, uh, Rathbone.
我在幫我的新書下標題
I was just thinking of a title for my new book.
洛依大戰娘娘腔閣下
"Roy O'Bannon vs. Little Lord Sissy"
如果叫  洛依大戰未來女皇
But what about
感覺怎麼樣?
"Roy O'Bannon vs. The Man Who Would Be Queen"?
沒他的蹤影
No sign of him, Chon.
這裡空空如也
The coast is clear up here.
洛依  小心!
Roy! Look out!
洛依!
Roy!
上來吧
Come on up.
讓你看看你父親是怎麼死的
I'll show you how your father died.
老天  救救我
Lord, help me.
讓我知道你的確有眼
just let me know you're there.
愛我  恨我
Love me. Hate me.
但至少讓我知道你存在
But let me know you're up there!
從這裡看得到我們住的旅館呢
Hey, I can see our hotel from here.
來啊
Come along.
我恭候大駕呢
I'm waiting.
加油  洛依  沒問題的
Come on, Roy. Okay.
洛依不會安靜等死的
Roy O'Bannon will not go quietly.
聽見嗎  英國?
You hear that, England?!
隨你怎麼待我
Throw whatever you want at me.
爛天氣
your terrible weather,
變態殺手
your perverted killers,
還有葡萄乾布丁
your Spotted Dick!
洛依  你快死了
Roy, you're about to die.
你的時間所剩無多
You're on the minute hand of a clock.
我的一生自眼前飛逝而過
My life is flashing before my eyes.
等等  她是誰啊?
Wait a minute. I don't remember her.
再來一次
One more.
對你太失望了
How disappointing.
再來一次
One more.
你害死了我朋友
You killed my friend.
殺死了我父親
You killed my father!
洛依
Roy!
我以為你死了
I thought you were dead! Oh!
你以為一個喝下午茶的變態
You think some tea-drinking psycho
就能幹掉我?
can take out Roy O'Bannon?
慢慢來  大牛仔
Easy there, cowboy.
有主意嗎?
You got any ideas?
-我們跳  -跳?
- We Jump! - Jump?!
你是說摔吧
You mean fall?!
抓住旗子
Aim for the flag!
我得告訴你
I got to tell you something.
什麼?
What?
你是這世上最棒的助手了
You're the best sidekick I could ever ask for.
謝謝  我對你也有同感
Thank you, Roy. I feel the same about you.
數到三
On three.
一
One...
-二  三
- Two! - Three!
洛依  洛依
Roy. Roy!
你好
Howdy.
為表彰你傑出的英勇行為
In recognition of outstanding bravery,
我封你為姜文爵士
I dub you Sir Chon Wen.
為表彰你的勇猛
For uncommon valor,
我封你為歐·洛依爵士
I dub you Sir Roy O'Bannon.
為表彰你堅守司法的崗位
And for steadfast dedication to justice,
我封你為亞瑟·柯南多伊爾爵士
I dub you Sir Arthur Conan Doyle.
請起
Arise.
誰最愛你啊  寶貝?
Who loves you, baby?
小姐
Madam.
我敢說警局又打算請你回去了
Artie, I bet Scotland Yard's dying to get you back now.
我對抗罪犯的日子結束了
My official crime-fighting days are over.
女皇邀我陪她一同
The queen has asked me to accompany
去中國還玉璽
the Imperial Seal back to China.
你是最佳人選
What a week. Unbelievable.
女王再找不到更合適的人了
She couldn't have picked a better man,
-對吧  姜?  -正是如此
- right, Chon? - Yeah.
而我也將有時間寫我的小說
And the voyage is gonna give me time to work on my new novel.
裏面將描繪一個全新的偵探
It features a new kind of detective, and
運用推理來解謎探案
he's gonna solve crimes using deductive reasoning.
他叫什麼名字?
Give me a name. What's his name?
我想如果你不介意的話
Actually, Roy, I was rather hoping
我想稱他夏洛克·福爾摩斯
to call him Sherlock Holmes,
你覺得合適嗎?
if That's all right with you.
你不用它我才會不爽
I'd be insulted if you didn't use it.
再會了
Ta. Artie.
你真好心  洛依
That was very nice of you, Roy.
好名字我才要留着
I would've kept the name if I thought it was any good.
那名字太爛了
It's a horrible name for a detective
夏洛克·福爾摩斯
Sherlock Holmes. Holmes?
你別再玩它了好嗎?
Will you stop playing with that?
-讓我看看  -不行
- I just want to see it for a second. - No!
-就看一會兒  -不行
- just let me see it. - No!
不  你會弄壞的
No, you're gonna break it.
只是顆刻了咒語的石頭嘛
It's just a rock with some gibberish on it.
這是中文
That's Chinese.
家人永遠是家人  吾兒
"Family is forever, my son.
我很驕傲你選了自己的路
I'm proud you cast your own stone."
真棒的訊息
That's a good message.
我也想選自己的路走
I'd like to cast my own stone, Chon.
我說過  歐氏莊園會興盛的
I told you the house of O'Bannon will prevail.
我有個事業提案
Chon, I got a business proposition for you.
-別再提飛船了  -不  不是的
- No more zeppelins. - No, no,
這比那更好
this is much better than zeppelins,
是加州新興的事業
a new thing they're starting out in California
叫電影
called moving pictures.
-算了  -等等  聽我說完嘛
- Pass. - Hold it. Hold it. Hear me out.
我真的認為電影能
I really think these movies
表現出你的力量
could play to your strength.
它沒有聲音
There's no sound, so we Don't have to
所以沒有語言問題
worry about the language problem.
我想功夫片一定會大賣
And I think the kung fu stuff could be huge.
人們最愛看動作片了
People are dying for a good action picture.
你覺得呢?
What do you think?
電影明星  姜文?
Chon Wen, movie star?
好像不錯
It could work.
我真不想丟下卓別林那小子
I feel bad about ditching that Chaplin kid,
但我們要去好萊塢
but we're gonna be running and gunning in Hollywood,
他會壞事的
and he'd just cramp our style.
那裡競爭可激烈了
It's such a tough town.
死觀光客!
Bloody tourists!
開拍
Action
你不能光顧着看
You have to say "cut."
你得喊卡啊
You just keep looking.
過來  你這隻小綿羊
Come here, you little minx.
-卡  -不錯
- Cut. - That was good.
這鏡頭不錯吧?
That was a good one, huh?
也許這回該我舔你
Maybe on this one I should
你覺得呢?
lick you, you think?
在你舔過我之後
Like, after you lick me.
應該不錯
that could be kind of good.
成龍
And, Jackie.
成龍?  謝了  歐文  你好
Thank you. Hi, Owen.
最近怎麼樣?
Hello. How are you?
我不是歐·洛依
Okay, and I'm not Roy O'Bannon.
那你是誰?
Who are you?
就是她了  我知道這很瘋狂
Damn it, Chon, I think She's the one.
我們才剛認識
I know It's crazy. We just met,
但就是她了
but She's the one.
洛依  她是我的褓姆
No, Roy, She's my babysitter.
你的褓姆?
Your babysi?
怎麼啦?
What?
什麼褓姆呀?  是小妹
Baby what? Baby sister.
小妹
Baby sister?
不是褓姆  是小妹
Not babysitter. Baby sister.
你沒事吧?
You okay?
開拍
Action!
怎麼回事?
What happened?
他是那種你不會介紹給朋友
Roy is the type of a friend you never introduce to
或帶回家的朋友
your other friends or bring into your family.
你看看他的眼睛...
He's... Look at his eyes.
棕色的  像屎一樣  總是...
They're brown, full of shit. Always...
就會唬弄別人
just bullshit all the time.
聽過父母這個詞嗎?
Yeah, have you ever heard of those?
我們是有父母疼愛的
They're parents. We have parents that love us.
你沒有  你是個小孤兒
You Don't, cause you're a little orphan.
你沒有  我們有  父母
You don't, We've got par, Yeah, parents.
你聽過這詞吧?
Have you ever heard of those?
我們是有父母疼愛的
We've got parents that love us.
你沒有  因為你是孤兒
But you Don't, cause you're a little orphan.
走開
Oh, go on.
真無情
So mean.
電影明星  姜文?
Chon Wen, movie star?
好像不錯
It could work.
是啊  你特技可以自己來
It could work. You could do your own stunts.
什麼  自己來?
What? My own stunts?
待在這兒
Stay here and be a good horsey
好好服侍新警長
for the new sheriff.
好痛
Ow. That hurt.
他沒事
He is fine.
你應該要接住我的
You're supposed to catch me!
洛依  接住
Roy, catch.
-主啊  -都是我的錯
- Jesus. - That's my fault.
等等
Wait a second.
這瘋子殺了妓女?
This nut is killing your street women?
是誰的?
Who did that?
成龍
Jackie Chan.
-我?  -沒錯
- Me? - That's right.
第一次  第一次
That was the. First time.
-這次的鏡頭最好  -對不起
- The best take. - I'm sorry.
快點!
Hurry up!
你瘋了  我做不到的!
Are you crazy? I can't do that!
這裡不是中國城  我不能飛
This isn't Chinatown! I can't sail through the air!
-我會摔斷脖子的  -洛依
- I'm not gonna break my neck! - Roy!
是什麼讓你
What in our history together makes you think
認為我能做到?
I'm capable of something like that?
火變大了
It's getting bigger!
一定有更好的辦法
There's got to be a better way.
洛依!
Roy!
靠!洛依!
我屁股着火了
My ass is on fire.